Christopher Combs

Systems Administrator | JavaScript Developer

Saint Petersburg, Florida US

Skilled systems administrator and applications developer with 10+ years of professional experience. Eager to offer analytical skills and first-class production support to help Humana fulfill it's values. In current role, supported two different SaaS applications and developed a chat bot to help with a transition phase.

WORK EXPERIENCE (5)

Site Reliability Engineer II at Humana June 2018- Current

A systems administrator for Workday, a cloud based HR SaaS. Provided troubleshooting, systems configuration and customer support to associates.

- Developed and designed the first instance of a IBM Watson chatbot to help associates at Humana become acclimated with Workday.
- Developed business intellgience on our shared support mailbox and a maintainer of our team knowledgebase.
- Assisted as a systems administrator on CornerStone a cloud based learning management SaaS when needed.

Systems Business Analyst at Humana November 2014- June 2018

Technical subject matter expert on Taleo Enterprise, a cloud based HR SaaS for recruiting and performance management. Provided consultation, configuration, training and customer support to Humana's people leaders.

- Helped with uncovering unused functionality within the Talent Center enabling better mid and yearly Performance Summaries.
- Provided end of life support for the sunsetting of the Talent Center as the company switched to Workday HCM.

Applications Engineer at Humana December 2012- November 2014

Designed, developed and implemented enterprise applications using Oracle Applications Express for Humana at Home.

- Redesigned a relationship management application for nurses, member services and others who manage the care of Humana's members.
- Developed a new application to maintain, notify and update nursing licensure instead of MS Excel spreadsheets.

Reporting Analyst at Humana November 2011- December 2012

Analyzed and provided descision making analytics for Humana RightSourceRx's call center to help switch members from brand drugs to generic drugs.

- Developed a system to replace MS Excel spreadsheets to help track members, leads, faxes and reporting on call events.
- Helped reduce staffing overhead and improved workflow automation saving our members over \$3 million in prescription savings.

Lead Pharmacy Technician at Humana November 2008- November 2011

VOLUNTEER ——

Disaster Action Team at American Red Cross **July 2014 - Current**

EDUCATION (1)

No Degree Pre-medicine at University 2010 - 2012